Guide to the Park City Mountain Resort audio-visual collection 1961-2002
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Team Deer Valley mogul skiing promotion / Bud Mogul Tour, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 272)
  In this video, Barry Johnson promotes the Deer Valley Pro Mogul team. The video also contains a news report on Park City's freestyle team which includes interviews with the team members and footage of them competing. Also included is ESPN's coverage of the Bud Mogul Tour.
- Park City Resort employee orientation, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 273)
  This tape contains Park City Mountain Resort's employee orientation, which focuses on customer service.
- Untitled videocassette, undated; Hi-8 videocassette (Cassette 274)